Nancy Sweezy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 5: Refugee Arts Group (RAG) and the Center for Living Traditions, 1985-1997, Bulk: 1986-1991
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Sok Prak - Cambodian Stone Carver, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_022; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Apprenticeship, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_023; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Refugee Arts Group book, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_001; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Survey, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph25_002; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Festival survey, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph25_003 to ph25_004; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Tong Xiong/ Striped Hmong/ Fitchburg, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_005; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Phanh Souvanna (Northern Lao) and Chia Yang Khang (Hmong), undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_006; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Kova Yang Lor Hmong, See Yang, Manolak Soyinthisane, Daolevang Chandaoleuang, and Kam Sivilai, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_007; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Manolak Soyinthisane and Ka Yeng Yang (Hmong), 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph25_008; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Hmong apprenticeship, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_009; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Kmhmu, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_010; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Lao silver bowls, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_011; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Saengsiri Group, Khamsone Silavong, and Kongkeo Chittarath - National Folk Festival, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_012; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Hiep Lam, Khene, Khamsone Silavong, and Saengsiri Group - National Folk Festival, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_013; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Saengsiri Group, Chantmachone, and Chom Thakham - National Folk Festival, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_014; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Peng Lovan/party for baby, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_015; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Lao New Year, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_016 to ph25_017; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Mouk Phon and Phan Bin, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_018; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Vathana Chea Group and Chorb Chan Group, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_019; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Kmhmu New Year, 1991, AFC 2017/001: ph25_020; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Kmhmu Sword Dance / Kim Chi Potter, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph25_021; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Khmer Performing Arts Ensemble / Cambodian New Year, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_022 to ph25_025; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Lowell Angkor dance troupe, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_026 to ph25_027; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Chorb Chan group in Lowell, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph25_028; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Chorb Chan group at Smithsonian, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph25_029; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Chorb Chan, Ger Her/Yee Her, Yang/Khang, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_030; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Cambodian New Year, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_031; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Manolak Soyinthisane - Lao Carver, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_032; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Davy Heder, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_033; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Ying Yang Lee - Springfield, Thanh Pham - Smith College, and Youen Chaun - Amherst, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_034; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Hiep Lam, Lundy Meas, and Fang Nou, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_035; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Vietnamese dragon dance program, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_036; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Hiep Lam, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_037; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Connecticut Khmer and Brockton Hmong, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_038; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Lao, Hmong, Khmer, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph25_039; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Apprenticeship, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_040; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Tien and Hiep Lam on bamboo lantern, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_041; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - UN Photos / Library of Congress, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_042; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Lao New Year, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph25_043; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_044 to ph25_068; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Living Traditions showcase, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_069; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Laotian party, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph25_070 to ph25_071; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_072 to ph25_074; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_075 to ph25_081; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
    - Laotian picnic, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph25_082; film negatives, black and white; 35 mm. (Box 46)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - A Dance from my Homeland Vietnam, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV01; 1 videotape
    - Southeast Asian Folk Art Festival - Boston, 1989-06, AFC 2017/001: MV02; 1 videotape
    - Angkor Dance Troupe performing at the Pickering Junior High School in Lynn, Massachusetts, 1990-11, AFC 2017/001: MV03; 1 videotape
    - Lang Her and Ger Her, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV04; 1 videotape
    - Vietnamese music at Smithsonian Folklife Festival / Nguyen Dinh Nghia family of the Metropolitan Washington Stage; Presented by Richard Kennedy, 1987-07, AFC 2017/001: MV09; 1 videotape
    - Cambodian Celebrations by Irene Starr - Amherst, Massachusetts; this is an 18-minute video about the Cambodian New Year, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV11; 1 videotape
    - Teng Yang and Xao Her, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV13; 1 videotape
    - Cambodian dance and talk, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV14; 1 videotape
    - Vietnamese Kin Chi potter, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV16; 1 videotape
    - TCM Festival 1989 / Southeast Asian Folk Art Festival, 1989-06-25, AFC 2017/001: MV17; 1 videotape
    - Kmhmu Apprenticeship, 1988-05, AFC 2017/001: MV18; 1 videotape
    - Members of the thrid grade at the Garfield School in Revere, Massachusetts, performing the Coconut Shell Dance; This performance, done in celebration of the Cambodian New Year, was the culmination of a four day residency program by Cambodian artist Tithra Soch., undated, AFC 2017/001: MV19; 1 videotape
    - Khao-I-Dang Pottery interview; Aranyapratet, Thailand, 1986-05, AFC 2017/001: SR033; 1 audio cassette
    - RAG Meeting with Cynthia Cohen; Arlington, 1987-01-05, AFC 2017/001: SR034; 1 audio cassette
    - RAG Meeting with Cynthia Cohen; Arlington, 1987-01-05, AFC 2017/001: SR035; 1 audio cassette
    - Southeast Asian Performances at Festival of the Lake; Oakland, California, 1991-06-01, AFC 2017/001: SR050; 1 audio cassette
- Series 6: Armenia, 1987-2008, Bulk: 1988-1997
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Notes on Armenia trips, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 63/4-6)
    - Armenia interview papers, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 63/7-8)
    - Interview with Kolia Torosian, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Armenia Cultural Project grants, 1991-2002 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Armenia Cultural Project grants, 1991-2002 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Armenia project photograph information, undated (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Armenia Cultural Project documentation and correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box-folder 64/3-8)
    - Armenia exhibit proposals, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 64/9-10)
    - Armenia exhibit proposals, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 65/1-2)
    - Armenia Cultural Project - Museum research and correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 65/3-4)
    - Exhibit in Armenia with Hamlet and Harut (Hamlet Petrosian and Harutyan Marutian), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 65/5-6)
    - Armenia Cultural Project fundraising, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 65/7-8)
    - Armenia Cultural Project outreach contact lists, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Armenia Cultural Project list of artists as of Sep., 1994 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Armenian crafts marketing, 1991-2002 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Armenian crafts marketing, 1991-2002, 13 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Proposal for an exhibition of Armenian folk art and ancient treasures with satellite programs and forums, 1994 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Armenia research, undated (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Armenia-SS [Sam Sweezy], 1987-1991, 196 photographic prints (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Armenia black and white, 1987-1991, 25 photographic prints (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Armenia SS [Sam Sweezy] color, 1987-1991, 55 photographic prints (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Armenia SS [Sam Sweezy] color cont, 1987-1991, 88 photographic prints (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Country Roads: Jugtown, Refugee Arts Group, Center for Living Traditions, Armenia, and portraits, undated, 70 photographic prints (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Armenia: Private Box, 1987-1991, 23 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Armenia Sam Sweezy color contact sheets, undated, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/20)
    - Arts of Armenia by Dickman Kouymjan - manuscript, 1993 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Info on videotapes shot in Armenia, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Armenia printed material, undated (Box-folder 66/6-11)
    - Armenia art and cultural research for the Silk Road Project and the 36th Annual Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Silk Road papers, 2002 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Silk Road, 2002, 39 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Armenia Cultural Project book plans, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Writings by Levon Abrahamian, undated (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Armenia book development with Levon Abrahamian, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 67/5-7)
    - Armenia book outlines, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Correspondence - Indiana University Press, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 67/9-12)
    - Correspondence - Indiana University Press, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Armenia book marketing, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Images considered for Armenia book, undated, 43 photographic prints (Box-folder 68/3-4)
    - Mount Ararat panorama, undated, 1 photographic print (Box-folder 90/1)
    - Armenia book drafts: Preface, foreword, and afterword, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 68/5-6)
    - Armenia book drafts: Notes, glossary, and bibliography, undated (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter one, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 68/8-9)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter two, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter two, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 69/1-6)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter three, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 69/7-11)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter four, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 70/1-8)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter five, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 70/9-10)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter five, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 71/1-2)
    - Armenia book drafts: Chapter six, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 71/3-10)
    - Armenia book draft: Afterword and notes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Armenia interview drafts, undated (Box-folder 72/2)
    - "A Tale of Culture and History in Armenia" by Nancy Sweezy (draft one), undated (Box-folder 72/3)
    - "A Tale of Culture and History in Armenia" by Nancy Sweezy (draft two), undated (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Armenia book reviews, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Armenia book talks, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Armenia working paper no. 1 for TV interviews - with photo index, 2008-2008 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - A Tale of Culture and History in Armenia by Nancy Sweezy - long paper, final version, 2008 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Picasa web album photo index - Armenian crafts, 2008 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Armenia Cultural Project and exhibit, 1994, afc2017001_cf07; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenian-American project, 1994-1995, afc2017001_cf07; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - London conference, 1994, afc2017001_cf07; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenia book, 1999, afc2017001_cf22; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Levon communications, 1999-2000, afc2017001_cf20; text files; original media: zip disk
    - From laptop 8/10/07 - Notes on Armenian Culture, 2007-08-10, afc2017001_cf01; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenia land and history, 2007-09-03, afc2017001_cf02; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenia - history and origins, identity, settlements, undated, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenia interview outlines, undated, afc2017001_cf05; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Armenia correspondence, undated, afc2017001_cf06; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Interview notes, Ernie Sarro, undated, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Country Roads store/Armenia, 1995, AFC 2017/001: ph09_095 to ph09_114 (Box 21-22)
    - Armenia, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph14_001 to ph14_027 (Box 29-30)
    - Artisans, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_028 to ph14_135 (Box 29-30)
    - Pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_136 to ph14_141 (Box 29-30)
    - Various crafts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_142 to ph14_155 (Box 29-30)
    - Textiles, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_156 to ph14_174 (Box 29-30)
    - Woodwork, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_175 to ph14_231 (Box 29-30)
    - Metalwork, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph14_232 to ph14_290 (Box 29-30)
    - Armenia, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_001 to ph15_098 (Box 30-33)
    - FA Museum, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_099 to ph15_199 (Box 30-33)
    - Weaving, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_200 to ph15_207 (Box 30-33)
    - Sadarabat Museum, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_208 to ph15_221 (Box 30-33)
    - Wood Museum, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_222 to ph15_234 (Box 30-33)
    - Children's Museum, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_235 to ph15_251 (Box 30-33)
    - Museum outside Yerevan, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_252 to ph15_257 (Box 30-33)
    - Goris, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_258 to ph15_300 (Box 30-33)
    - Demi-tasse factory, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_301 to ph15_314 (Box 30-33)
    - Khachkars, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_315 to ph15_321 (Box 30-33)
    - Lake Savan and fort, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_322 to ph15_330 (Box 30-33)
    - Monasteries, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_331 to ph15_365 (Box 30-33)
    - Trip with Aram to ancient site, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_366 to ph15_382 (Box 30-33)
    - Grisha's Pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_383 to ph15_425 (Box 30-33)
    - Rubin Hakverdian, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_426 to ph15_436 (Box 30-33)
    - Music instrument maker, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_437 to ph15_446 (Box 30-33)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph15_447 to ph15_474 (Box 30-33)
    - Assortment for slide shows - Sam's set, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph16_001 to ph16_127 (Box 33-34)
    - Assortment for slide shows - Scenery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph16_128 to ph16_147 (Box 33-34)
    - Assortment for slide shows - Armenian crafts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph16_148 to ph16_167 (Box 33-34)
    - Assortment for slide shows - Armenian people, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph16_168 to ph16_178 (Box 33-34)
    - Khachars, monasteries, and architecture, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph17_001 to ph17_518 (Box 34-37)
    - Unlabeled, 1994, AFC 2017/001: ph18_001 to ph18_571 (Box 37-40)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - "Armenia Through a Potter's Eye: Part One" The Expert Series, Ernie Sarro and Todd Mahoney; Guest Nancy Sweezy, 2008, afc2017001_cf14; Digital video; run time 01:01:02; original media: optical disk
    - Virtuozi of Armenia, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV15; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 1 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV21; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 2 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV22; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 3 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV23; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 5 / W. Lambrecht, Kolia Torossian, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV24; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 6 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV25; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 7 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV26; 1 videotape
    - Armenia number 8 / W. Lambrecht, 1991, AFC 2017/001: MV27; 1 videotape
    - Side one: Woodwork Shop in Yerevan / Side two: Metal shop with Antsnoum "Berbenian"; Yerevan, Armenia, 1990-06-18, AFC 2017/001: SR036; 1 audio cassette
    - Eugenia Ohanian; Yerevan, Armenia, 1990-06-22, AFC 2017/001: SR037; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Ararat Martinossian on wood work no. 5 / Side two: Kolia Torosian on musical instruments; Interviews in Bambakashat and Byurakan, Armenia, 1990-06-23, AFC 2017/001: SR038; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Kolia Torosian on musical instruments cont. / Side two: Interview at rug shop and iron shop; Interviews on musical instruments in Byurakan, Armenia; rug weaving and blacksmithing in Yerevan, Armenia, 1990-06-25, AFC 2017/001: SR039; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Mayor of Yerevan and Hambartoun Galstian / Side two: Discussion with Levon Abrahamian and other scholars at Sadarapat Museum; Wood worker in Yerevan, Armenia, 1990, AFC 2017/001: SR040; 1 audio cassette
    - Cont. Antsnoum Berberian, Pottery - Asatrian, and Eugenia Ohanian; Metal work in Yerevan, Armenia and pottery in Artashat, Armenia, 1990-06, AFC 2017/001: SR041; 1 audio cassette
    - Ruben - wood miniatures and pendants; Yerevan, Armenia, 1991-05-10, AFC 2017/001: SR042; 1 audio cassette
    - Ophelia Ohanian on rug weaving; Ijevan, Armenia, 1991-05-13, AFC 2017/001: SR043; 1 audio cassette
    - Haikis Martirossian on pottery no. 3; Bambakashat, Armenia, 1991-05-15, AFC 2017/001: SR044; 1 audio cassette
    - Cont. Haikis Martirossian on pottery no. 3; Bambakashat, Armenia, 1991-05-15, AFC 2017/001: SR045; 1 audio cassette
    - Ararat Martirossian no. 4; Bambakashat, Armenia, 1991-05-16, AFC 2017/001: SR046; 1 audio cassette
    - Rug weaving factory and Pottery; Goris, Armenia, 1991-05-17, AFC 2017/001: SR047; 1 audio cassette
    - Grisha Aratrian at his pottery shop; Shahumian, Georgia, 1991-05-20, AFC 2017/001: SR048; 1 audio cassette
    - Woodcarvers, 1991-05-21, AFC 2017/001: SR049; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Antsnoun Berberian on jewelry and metal work / Side two: Rouben Hakverdian on woodworking; Both homes in Yerevan, Armenia, 1991-10-28, AFC 2017/001: SR051; 1 audio cassette
    - Rouben Hakhverdian on woodworking at his studio; Yerevan, Armenia, 1991-10-29, AFC 2017/001: SR052; 1 audio cassette
    - Samson Chagarian on pottery; Goris, Armenia, 1991-10-31, AFC 2017/001: SR053; 1 audio cassette
    - Samson Chagarian on pottery; Goris, Armenia, 1991-10-31, AFC 2017/001: SR054; 1 audio cassette
    - Harant Bagdagelian on pottery; Goris, Armenia, 1991-10-31, AFC 2017/001: SR055; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview of Gagik blacksmith shop; Yerevan, Armenia, 1991-11-02, AFC 2017/001: SR056; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview of Seroj Assadourian on pottery, 1991-11-03, AFC 2017/001: SR057; 1 audio cassette
    - Kolia Torossian on musical instruments, 1991-11-04, AFC 2017/001: SR058; 1 audio cassette
    - Music and dance in village, 1991-11-10, AFC 2017/001: SR059; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview of rug weaver; Yerevan, Armenia, 1991, AFC 2017/001: SR060; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview of Margarita Broudian, 1991, AFC 2017/001: SR061; 1 audio cassette
    - Grecia Aradourian and Armenian churches, 1991, AFC 2017/001: SR062; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview with Grecia Aradourian on pottery, 1992-06-09, AFC 2017/001: SR063; 1 audio cassette
    - Kolia Torossian making and playing musical instruments, 1992-06-12, AFC 2017/001: SR064; 1 audio cassette
    - Hripsime tape of interviews of Leana, 1992-06-13, AFC 2017/001: SR065; 1 audio cassette
    - Scholars at Sadarapat, 1992-06-25, AFC 2017/001: SR066; 1 audio cassette
    - Sadarapat meeting with scholars, undated, AFC 2017/001: SR067; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview with Levon Abrahamian, Haroutian Maroutian, Hamlet Petrosian, and Svetlana Poghosian; Hamlet Petrosian - medieval life, Poghsian - folk clothing, 1992-06, AFC 2017/001: SR068; 1 audio cassette
    - Peter Rowan and Kesta Smith performing in Martiros Sarya Park; Yerevan, Armenia, 1992-10-03, AFC 2017/001: SR069; 1 audio cassette
    - Meeting with Levon Abrahamian, Hamlet Petrosian, Haroutian Maroutian, and Hrijsima Pikitchian, 1992-10-04, AFC 2017/001: SR070; 1 audio cassette
    - Cont. meeting with Levon Abrahamian, Hamlet Petrosian, Haroutian Maroutian, and Hrijsima Pikitchian, 1992-10-04, AFC 2017/001: SR071; 1 audio cassette
    - Discussion with Levon Abrahamian; Review and discussion at Levon's house in Yerevan, Armenia, 1992-10-05, AFC 2017/001: SR072; 1 audio cassette
    - Scholars meeting at Aram's, 1992-10-10, AFC 2017/001: SR073; 1 audio cassette
    - Sadarapat Museum with Hamlet Petrosian and Ashkoonj Pogosian on rugs, 1992-10-06, AFC 2017/001: SR074; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Interview with mayor of Yerevan / Side two: Sadarapat meeting, 1992, AFC 2017/001: SR075; 1 audio cassette
- Series 7: Spirited Objects and OXYGEN Media Project, 1996-2001, Bulk: 1998-2001
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Spirited Objects - Origins: Nancy Sweezy and Dan Sheehy, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Spirited Objects development, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Spirited Objects - National Endowment for the Arts grants, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Spirited Objects - American Crafts Exhibition advisors and Henry Glassie, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Spirited Objects planning, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Spirited Objects planning notebook, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Spirited Objects - White House initiative, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - Spirited Objects photos and correspondence, 1998, 60 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Spirited Objects photos and correspondence, 1998, 44 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Spirited Objects slide index, undated (Box-folder 73/8)
    - Barbara Barber quilter: Rhode Island, undated, 13 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Northeast woodwork: exhibit in Maine, 1998, 32 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Ora Watson, 2000, 16 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/1)
    - North Carolina: Hufford's in Vale, North Carolina, 1998, 10 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Cherokee baskets, undated, 9 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Louisiana baskets, undated, 7 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Cannon City baskets, undated, 4 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/5)
    - North Carolina site visit, 1994, 4 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Neil Graves and Lucille Swen, undated, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Ben Owen, undated, 5 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Mark Hewitt, undated, 5 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Kim Ellington, undated, 5 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Interview notes and photos: Steve Abee - Mountain Potter (Lenoir, North Carolina), 1998, 3 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/9)
    - Interview notes and photos: Burlon Craig - Mountain Potter (Vale, North Carolina), 1998, 15 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/10)